现在喷射通风我属于我
now jet ventilation i'm belonging to I'm
从那以后一直坚持喷射通风
staying on jet ventilation then since
十多年来绝对是这样
more than a decade it's the absolutely
在我的膝盖和我的主要护士的必要性
necessity in my lap and my main nurse
每天早上开始穿上喷气式飞机
starts every morning to put on the jet
呼吸机，走出实验室
ventilator and goes out of the lab in
下午或晚上放
the afternoon or in the evening and put
它关闭所以它始终是主要的必需品
it off so it's always the main essential
我实验室里的东西现在是主要的东西之一
stuff in my lab now one of the main
喷射通风的优点很简单
advantages of jet ventilation is simply
它为您提供了一个多余的事实
the fact that it offers you one excess
用于通风和干预
for ventilation and intervention at the
同一时间，如果你现在比较
same time and if you compare now the
第二张图片在这里你有很多
second picture here you have a lot of
更多空间更多空间
much more more space more space to
从声门上观点干预
intervene from a supraglottic view and
对于很多人来说也是如此
this is as well true for a lot of
现在在肺部应用生理学
applications in the lung now physiology
喷射通风是一个非常复杂的问题
of jet ventilation is a very complex
事情是你的主要事情之一
thing one of the main things what you
必须要明白的是，对于喷气式飞机
have to understand is that for a jet
通风你总是要有一个
ventilation you always have to have an
开放式通风是主要的通风之一
open ventilation that's one of the main
第二个是你拥有的东西
things the second one is that you have
始终有灵感探索
to have always inspiration exploration
在同一时间和其中一个
at the same time and one of the the
第三件事就是你必须成为
third things is that you have to be
意识到有些患者有
aware that some of the patients have a
胸壁顺应性问题如此
problem with thoracic wall compliance so
只有极少数患者
there are only a very few patients which
是你不能应用喷气机的地方
is where you cannot apply jet
通风不到一个
ventilation that's less than one
我认识的所有患者的百分比
percentage of all the patients I knew
现在，如果你寻找让我们说的更老
now if you look for let's say the older
你只有聊天通风的形式
forms of chat ventilation you only have
一个频率和关于
one frequency and in regards to
您可以选择生理学
physiology you either can choose with a
低频或高频带
low frequency or a high frequency with a
低频意味着你可以诱导
low frequency that means you can induce
潮气通风较高
tidal ventilation with a higher
例如，你可以增加频率
frequency you can increase for example
使用你的窥视，这意味着氧气，但
use your peep that means oxygenation but
如果你结合其中两种方法，如果
if you combine two of these means so if
你有一台为你提供正常的机器
you have a machine offering you a normal
频率射流和更高频率的射流
frequency jet and a higher frequency jet
同时你可以叠加这些
at the same time you can overlay these
两种生理学，为您提供
two physiologies and that offers you
控制po2和po2时有很大的优势
great advantages as you control po2 and
pco2同样如此
pco2 at the same
时间，如果你申请这个你还有一个
time if you apply this you still have a
双级
bi-level
通风，但你有两个层面
ventilation but on both levels you have
仍在振荡，由此而来
still oscillation and by this
振荡你可以减少pco2
oscillation you can reduce pco2 by less
高原压力这是一个伟大的
plateau pressures this is a great
与传统相比的优势
advantage in comparison to conventional
像电力这样的潮汐通风
tidal ventilation like by power and this
如果你看，发表得很好
is well very well published if you look
进入较老的文献 - 来自
into the literature that's older - from
2012年显示，如果你比较
2012 showing that if you compare
叠加更高频率的射流
superimpose higher frequency jet
正常喷射通风换气
ventilation with normal jet ventilation
然后你可以看到氧合作用
then you can see that the oxygenation is
更好，以及pco2清除
better as well as the pco2 clearance is
更好，这是pco2清除
better so that is the pco2 clearance
这是氧合作用，它会好得多
that's the oxygenation it's much better
比正常频率喷射通风
than normal frequency jet ventilation
现在Carl Reiner介绍了双胞胎
now Carl Reiner has introduced the twin
流和卡琳娜作为一家公司
stream and Karina as a company from
奥地利设计了很多
Austria has designed a lot of
最适合双倍的仪器
instruments optimal for the double
频率喷射通风这是其中之一
frequency jet ventilation this is one of
你可以得到它的例子
the examples you can get it for ent
问题，但也适用于僵化
problem but as well for for rigid
支气管镜在正常肺部
bronchoscopy in the normal pulmonary
这是双胞胎的监视器
area this is the monitor of the twin
流你也可以申请
stream you can apply as well ite
关系以及高频率
relations as well for the high frequency
以及当然的低频率
as well for the low frequency of course
你可以申请
you can apply the
工作压力很容易
working pressure which is in easy
设置仅与中继相关或链接
settings only relay related or linked to
体重越复杂
the body weight for the more complex
你可以做的程序或观点
procedures or views you can you can
手动设置你有变量
setup it manually you have variable
像激光功能这样的功能
functions like laser function here for
例如，你有完整的实时
example you have complete real-time
测量所有珍贵的
measurement of all the precious which
诱导这样，我相信这很容易
induce so and I believe it's a very easy
而且安全意味着它是一台非常好的机器
and safe mean it's a very good machine
我的意思是非常着名的应用程序
and I mean very well known applications
胸外科和ICU in ent但是as
thoracic surgery and ICU in ent but as
以及干预肺病学
well an intervention pulmonology me
我亲自使用它或多或少700
personally I'm using it more or less 700
目前每年800次
to 800 times per year at the moment
国际肺病学
international pulmonology as well
我将展示介入心脏病学
interventional cardiology I will show
你以后的一些例子现在有些
you that later on some examples now some
人们认为喷射通风是
people believe that jet ventilation is
仍然是危险的事情
still a dangerous thing that is
绝对不是你有一个实时的
definitely not true you have a real-time
压力监测，所以你不必
pressure monitoring so you don't have to
只要你坚持，就要担心借创伤
fear borrow trauma as long as you keep
那个访问开放你有一个
that access open you have a
您可以控制的加湿系统
humidification system you can control
分别叠加在频率上
separately by superposed on frequency
喷射通风po2和pco2由两者组成
jet ventilation po2 and pco2 by the two
如果你想要不同的频率
different frequencies if you want to
以一种简单快捷的方式应用它
apply it in an easy and quick way you
只查找基于重量的参数
only look for weight based parameters
当然还有很多
and of course there are a lot of
该双胞胎认证的仪器
instruments certified for that twin
流我们现在在2008年发表于此
stream now we published in 2008 in this
或多或少我们分析的注册表
more or less registry we analyzed in
百病人3,300米
hundred patient 3,300 meters
测量，这是一个典型的
measurements and this is a typical
应用，因为我们在非刚性中使用它
application as we use it in non rigid
接近，所以我们使用那个喷射帽
approaches so we use that jet cap that's
我们可以做的双腔帽
a double lumen cap in which we can do
或多或少我们能做的一切
more or less everything which we can do
以及旁边的刚性显微镜
as well over rigid microscopy beside
喷气式飞机凯西有急诊室，我有另一个
that jet Kathy has ER and I have another
灵活的解决方案，这是一个喷射管
flexible solution that's a jet tube
这是我们喜爱的特别设计的电子管
that's a specially designed tube we love
这种方法非常多，因为它给出了
this approach very much because it gives
我们以及整流罩的稳定性
us as well stability in the fairings for
例如，舌头就是这样
the tongue for example and it's very
容易放
easy to put
在吉米，我必须支付
in Jimmy I have to pay the
麻醉师如此一小时
anesthesiologist so one hour of
麻醉学费用为250至300欧元
anesthesiology costs me 250 to 300 euro
这节省了我大约200欧元
and that saves me around 200 euro per
现在，如果你进入指标和
case now if you go into the metrics and
你可以在文学中看到
of literature you can see that in the
过去三年你有四倍
last three years you have a four-fold
增加鼻腔喷射通气所以
increase about nasal jet ventilation so
这是一个即将到来的方法，我只想要
it's an upcoming method and I just want
向您展示我们的一些例子
to show you some of the examples what we
在我的实验室做，所以这是一个很抱歉
do in my lab so this is a so sorry for
音频不起作用
that the audio is not working at the
那一刻哦，你可以听到你能听到它
moment oh you can hear you can hear it
是的，所以你听到了喷气式呼吸机
yeah so that you hear the jet ventilator
在后台，你看到没有
in the background and you see there's no
肺运动虽然我们去转移
lung movement although we go transfer
酸用于导航小方法所以
acid for navigated small approach so
这或多或少都是介入性的
that is more or less interventional
放射学这是在冷却下完成的
radiology this is done under cooling
飞利浦目前的城市清晰度
City at the moment from Philips clarity
这是IBA的一次破坏所以它是一个
this is a puncture of IBAs so it's a
心包过量心包过量
pericardial excess pericardial excess by
我们在2016年发布的IBAs是
IBAs we published this in 2016 we are
经常这样做，你可以在这里看到它
doing that regularly you can see it here
你在这里再次拒绝你
you all you again here the reject
你看到背景中的呼吸机
ventilator in the background you see the
针在心包
needle in the pericardium
你看到跳动的心脏，没有
you see beating heart and nothing
我们绝对必不可少
happens we absolutely essential thing
为此，这种方法就是你
for this for this approach is that you
完全控制报警权和
have perfect control of alarm right and
这就是我们可以避免的事情
that's what we can avert let's will be
用他们的鼻喷射器实现
achieved with a their nasal jet
通风我们这样做是为了分析
ventilation we do that for analysis of
心包积液你可以看我怎么样
pericardial effusion you can see how I
缩回检索心包
retract retrieve that pericardial
积液现在再次很容易应用
effusion now again very easy application
这是在我们听到的热成形术期间
this is during thermoplasty as we heard
再来一次，你必须有一个非常
before again you have to have a very
良好的肺部控制，这是
good control of the lung and this is the
定期安装喷气式呼吸机
regular set up the the jet ventilator
你没有在月球上看到它，但你可以
you don't see it at the moon but you can
也许你会听到它
maybe you hear it in the in the
再次背景这是一个过激行为
background again it's a the excesses
再次鼻腔喷射通气所以
again the nasal jet ventilation so
没什么特别的
nothing special
但绝对控制肺部
but absolutely control about the lung
再次是微波炉的问题
again is the issue during microwave
我们使用的消融转移辅助方法
ablation transfer assic approach we use
在这里，我们测量时间
it like this here we measured the times
开/关表，例如当你
on/off table for example when you
比较这种插管方法
compare this approach to intubation
麻醉学它更快更快
anesthesiology it is much faster and
它更容易我们只需要10分钟
it's easier we only need 10 minutes of
从表中拿出阿尔法纸
taking on alpha paper out of the table
如果你去放松的话
and if you go for relaxation as it is
完成麻醉学你需要花费很多
done with anesthesiology you take much
更长的时间，所以快速快速容易
longer time so very quick fast easy
我们控制微波消融
we control during microwave ablation
例如出血也是如此
bleeding for example as well with that
仪器让放射科医生喜欢
instrument so the radiologists love the
接近你有完美的控制权
approach you have perfect control of
肺部运动，你可以在这里看到它
lung movement as you can see it here
完美的控制，你真的可以告诉
perfect control you really can tell the
什么都没有介入放射科医生
interventional radiologists when nothing
正在发生的事情，你仍然
is happening in the line and you still
现在已经控制了血气
have control of the blood gases now as
一件事是我们可以使用它
well one thing is that we can use that
聊天帽作为僵硬站立的意思
chat cap as a mean for rigid standing
虽然这意味着我们已经应用了这个J.
though that means we've applied this J
站在脓毒性布兰卡瘘我们
standing in a septic Branca fistula we
在鼻腔上应用注册和部署
applied register and deployment on nasal
喷射咳嗽
jet cough
所以这意味着我们开始穿夹克
so it means we started with a jacket for
在那个脓毒症患者和
ventilation in that septic patient and
然后我们应用了cha-cha刚性
then we applied over the cha-cha rigid
正确地部署支架以便提供
to deploy the stand right so that gives
当你开始时，你会更安全
you more security when you start that
过程，例如非常关键
process and for example very critical
患者这是另一个例子
patients this is another example where
我们申请不同的工作
we apply with different working
气管中的参数是一个
parameters in the trachea so that was a
每个鼻腔和管腔脓肿
per nasal and the luminal abscess
排水那是你的小腿小腿
drainage that's a7f pigtail calf you had
进入那个需要保守的警告
to get into that caveat you have to keep
以捷豹为例打开它
it open by that Jaguar for example
有通风夹克
there's the jacket for ventilation on
另一边
the other side
这就是我销售Viktor的原因
and that's me the selling of Viktor this
这样做是灵活的，不是僵硬的
is done flexible not rigid right so
再次便宜快速轻松快速擅长
again cheaper fast easy quick excels
而且总有一点是要记住这一点
and always one point is to remember that
你有情况，你有
you have situations where you have the
应用所谓的数字化
to apply the so-called digital
例如，通风
ventilation that is for example
有时错综复杂的岩石撕裂或
sometimes intricate rocky lacerations or
你必须去的跟踪手术
tracker surgery where you have to go
超出你的问题通风和
beyond your problem to ventilate and
再次，这很容易做到
again this is very easy to be done by
由喷气式直升机喷射的喷气式飞机
the jet by the jet copter that was a
我们已经注意到的情况和
case where we've fixated and and the
卡车将穿过小鸟针
truck will stand through a birdie needle
在那里，我和Versa一起长大
there you I grew up with the Versa
针头，他们有一个抓取器
needle that they have a grabber to get
但要获得那条线，如果我有
that but to get that line and if I had
从上面通风，你知道我们
ventilated from above you know then we
你下面有很多动静
had a lot of movement from below you
知道我们抓住它会容易得多
know it's much easier for us to to grab
那东西这是茶壶的情况
that thing this is a tea pot case so
通过导航和你的相关频道
related channel by a navigation and you
我可以再次看到没有肺部运动
can see again no lung movement all I
有绝对时间旋转我的ENB
have absolutely time to rotate my ENB
限制进入那个模块
cap right to get into that module that
大约18毫米90毫米
was around 18 millimeters 90 millimeters
并且是一种类癌，这也是
and was a carcinoid and again this is
绝对是完整和必要的
absolutely a necessity of complete and
完美的学习控制权我们使用它
perfect learn control right we use it
有时候收费也是如此
sometimes as well in charges so for lvr
例如，我们试图证明是否负载
for example we try to prove if the load
间接通风或密集
is dense by indirect ventilation or
直接通风的叶片本身
direct ventilation of the lobe itself so
我们可以用喷射器证明
we can prove with a with a jet
间接通风如果是
ventilation in an indirect mean if the
现在我想要的是耳垂非常密集
lobe is really dense now I just want to
向您展示我的锥形束CT实验室的一个案例
show you one case of my cone beam CT lab
那是一位667岁的女士
that was a lady 667 years old she had
这些结节三年就是这样
these nodules for three years so that is
结节大约11毫米和一个
a nodule about 11 millimeters and one
80毫米的模型都是
model of 80 millimeters it was both
支气管和阳性和血管我
bronchus and positive and vessels I'm
积极的现在似乎不是那样
positive now seems to be not that
很复杂，但你可以看到会发生什么
complicated but you can see what will
现在发生的是清晰度社区
happen now that's the clarity community
我使用清晰度我从一开始就知道
I use clarity I've been known since one
半年，所以我们改变了
and a half years so we changed from
西门子到
Siemens to
重力是由于一些经济原因
gravity that was due to some economical
这台机器的一个优点是
things one advantage of that machine is
你可以应用整体的一切
that you can apply everything the whole
现在你没有实验室规划
planning in the lab now you don't have
去外面是啊有一些
to go outside yeah there are some
缺点例如你不能
disadvantages for example you cannot
菲利普斯从头上引导帽子
steer the Hat by Phillips from the head
本身你有西门子的一些旋钮
itself you have some knobs with Siemens
你现在可以这么做了
you can do that now we used these days
我们e / m和机器所以美敦力
we the e/m and machine so the Medtronic
系统现在我们也改为支气管
system now we change to bronchus as well
我们有vbn和commune的组合
we have a combination of vbn and commune
现在的城市，但我们设法得到
city now but however we managed to get
那里和我们看到的是我们已经让我们
there and what we saw is we had let's
说预先计划的相当好的叠加
say quite good overlay of a pre-planned
扁平的路径，然后我们试着看到它
flat path and then we try to see it with
我们的MB与我们的宜必思酒店在一起
our MB with our Ibis and it was around
12点钟我们不满意
12 o'clock we were not satisfied with
我们已经完成了另一个km城市和我们
that we've done another km city and we
可以看到结节分开了
could see that the nodules separated
在这里操纵你可以看到
during the manipulation here you can see
那不只是分开你再次做到了
that not just separated you did it again
设法进入该模块和
managed to get into into that module and
再次在这里你可以看到2d的叠加
again here you can see the overlay of 2d
和3D以及MV活动当然
and 3d and the MV activity and of course
他看到了它总是依赖的运动
he see the movement it always depends on
控制肺过度充气
the control of the lung hyperinflation
再这就是你控制的东西了
so again that's what you control with a
根据杰克呼吸机
Jack ventilator according to the
珍贵的，这是肺部肿瘤
precious and this was emitted lung tumor
所以第一个房客不是恶性的
so the first lodger was not malignant
现在这个案子很有意思
now the interesting thing in that case
当我们试图弄清楚这是什么时
was as we tried to figure out what this
模块又是一个超过三个的金莺
module was again an Oriole over three
我们在EN看到的岁月，我们总能做到
years we saw in EN and we always could
达到那部分而不是那部分，所以我们
reach that part not that part so we
再次分割该模块，我们只
segmented again that module and we only
我想进入那个区域就是为什么
wanted to get into that area that's why
我们再做一次转移资产所以a
we did it again transfer asset so a
植物3d转移资产方法和
plant 3d transfer asset approach and
这是脂质ik腺癌
this was a lipid ik adenocarcinoma be
旁边是一个omlette肺肿瘤所以我们是
beside an omlette lung tumor so we were
很有趣的情况，这一切都是
quite interesting case and all this is
完成了社区和喷射通风
done and a community and jet ventilation
现在来看看Ender's for nasal
now to come to the Ender's for me nasal
口气是喷射通气，特别是鼻腔
tone is jet ventilation especially nasal
喷射通风是绝对的
jet ventilation is an absolutely
必要性和干预性肺病学
necessity and intervention pulmonology
我们正在做大约70起案件
and we're doing about 70 cases in on
用喷射器定期接近
regular lap approaches with jet
通风，你不必担心任何
ventilation you do not have to fear any
barotrauma你我们有一个非常安全的二氧化碳
barotrauma you we have a very safe co2
在那篇论文中我们消除了
elimination in that one paper we
发表我们找不到任何风险信号
published we couldn't find any risk sign
关于身体的年龄
in regards to age in regards to body
心脏和心脏的重量
weight in regards to heart and
充足，例如它就是一切
sufficiency for example it's all very
很好地发表所以唯一的事情是
well published so the only thing was
平均42分钟后
that after an average time of 42 minutes
我们看到pco2略有增加
we saw a little increase of pco2 on
平均但我们已经不再知道了
average but we have no longer known none
这些病人必须通风
of these patients had to be ventilated
通过正常的管通风我们已经
by normal tube ventilation and we've
做了多达四个半的干预
done interventions up to four and a half
小时只能通过鼻腔喷射通气
hours only by nasal jet ventilation so
在德国，它为我们节省了很多钱
in germany it saves us a lot of money
她的情况现在大约200欧元，不知何故
her case around 200 euro now and somehow
你知道那个视频是其中之一
you know that that video that was one of
我认为第一部电影是MCT
the first film MCT is I think in
上海的时候我们也做到了
Shanghai when we've done that as well
我喜欢这段视频
with the twin stream I love that video
我总是表现出来因为
still I always show it because
这是一个非常美好的一天，我们做了三个
it's a very nice day we've done three
当天有现场诉讼的案件
cases during that day with live suit
我现在在这里进行ology和生命干预
ology and life intervention now here I'm
戴上喷气帽
putting the jet cap
你飞了双流然后你
you're flying the twin stream then you
完美掌控你所做的路线
have perfect control of the line you do
CT中梳子的恐龙牙齿
the dinosaur teeth of the comb in CT
随你
whatever
- 在这种情况下的奶酪，然后你
- of cheese's in this case and then you
有该模块的细分
have the segmentation of that module
你不知道它不是那么小
it was not that small however you know
这些日子是第一次
for these days it was the first time
在2015年，然后你分段路径
in 2015 and then you segment the path in
这些情况我们碰巧做了
these cases we happen to do
一个T-box所以我们有一个野马标志
a t-box so we had a Bronco sign
在这件事中，这是第一个
in the thing these were the first
关于培训中心的讨论
discussions about the training center
你现在在上海有关于
which you now have in Shanghai about the
社区中心
community center
所以这是一个非常复杂的领域
so that's a very sophisticated area to
学习所有这些技术
learn all these technologies
只是让它证明它也是
just let it prove it's too
这是人们了解的方式
and it's so the people understand how
代码Masucci工作
code Masucci works
现在你有了所见的3D模型
now you have the 3d model as you see on
地板哦，你真的没有看到
the floor oh you don't see really that
一种病变
kind of of lesion
你做了一个三角形的角度我们
and you do a three-edged angulations we
看看3d和2d是如何重叠的
see how the 3d and 2d overlays that's
相当不错的叠加我们居中
quite a good overlay we are centered
这里
here
我们对活检有很高的特异性
we have a high specificity of biopsy
因为我们已经控制了它
because we have controlled it with our
伊娃也是，这是一个模具
Eva's as well and that was a mold
相关淋巴瘤
associated lymphoma
很难得到这么多
so quite difficult to to get so many
谢谢你的邀请
thanks for the invitation
我成了2美元以下的实用专利
nigga under $2 utility patent I became
今天她到达了她的数字我可以
who she reached her today number I can
讲协奏曲得到一个坚实的锤子
tell of concerto get a solid hammer the
我可以使用我自己的秘密来获得一个
console can I use my own secret he got a
先生。 namagachi Angela的问题
mr. namagachi Angela question
谢谢你谢谢你的精彩
thank you thank you for your wonderful
演讲，我知道双胞胎很紧张
speech and I know twin strain is very I
认为它的原因非常好
think it's very good at it cause in
中国我们使用高频率
China we use a high frequency high
频率通气多年
frequency ventilation for many years
你在中国认识的中国党
party in China you know in China the
高频呼吸机只有一个
high frequency ventilator just only one
邻居压力所以，但作为一个叽叽喳
neighbor pressure so but as a twittering
堆积所以我们不能把pso2等同起来
pile ever so we can't equate the pso2
我说过我们是最重要的
I said that us is the most important
为高频率的时间
time for the for the high frequency
后来的传统，但你好
which later for tradition but hello in
一般在我们得到你有一个
general in we we got a you got a
关注卡塔尔最关于她的事
attention Qatar nicest about her about
她使用或在可怜的权利
her use of or in the wretched right to
支气管镜检查晚会但它仍然会
the bronchoscopy gala but it will still
包含有关ARP分配的本质
contain essence about the ARP assignment
我的意思是她非常有趣
I mean very interesting about her the
用于你使用适当的字符串
use out for you use opportune string in
我们的情况当然我们使用我没有
our case so of course we use I haven't
表明你知道我们当然会使用
shown that you know of course we use the
双流以及刚性键合cos
twin stream as well and rigid bond cos
正如我解释的那样，再次在德国复制
copy but in Germany again as I explained
之前我想要使用刚性
before when I want to use rigid
支气管镜检查我要邀请我
bronchoscopy I have to invite my
麻醉师来我的实验室
anesthesiologist to come to my lab and
我们必须付钱给他们
we have to pay them right so that
增加了我部门的成本
increases the costs in my department
每当我们可以做的事情
whenever we can do things in
我们尝试应用干预肺病学
intervention pulmonology we try to apply
杰克，鼻子刺戳通气
the nasal jabbed ventilation the Jack
我展示的小牛或灵活的小牛
calf as I shown or the the flexible
有一个特殊的柔性管
there's a special flexible tube which
你既可以灵活又有灵活性
you can ply as well as a flexible
支气管镜检查
bronchoscopy
然而，这节省了我的成本和
however that saves me costs and the
我已经展示了一百张纸
paper which I have shown with a hundred
案件和3300只完成了
cases and 3300 was only done with
灵活的应用程序不严格
flexible applications not rigid
应用程序，我们还没有看到任何
applications and we haven't seen any
危险的标志，所以没有问题
danger sign so there was no problem at
全部用于po2，也不用于pco2
all for po2 and as well not for pco2
哪里没有真正的危险
where there was not really a dangerous
大约100例pco2增加
increase of pco2 in about hundred cases
你知道这样做了7075例IP
you know so 7075 cases were done for IP
干预25例
and 25 cases were done for intervention
心脏病学和干预放射学
cardiology and to intervention radiology
这么安全很容易
so very safe very easy to
为什么是谢谢你
why yes thank you